Di YUE

UI DESIGNER

INFO

ADDRESS

Rhodes, Sydney NSW

PHONE

(+61) 0410-918-668

shirleyyuedi@gmail.com

Permanent Resident

PORTFOLIO

https://shirleydy.github.io/

SKILLS

Stroyboarding

Wireframing

Prototyping

User Research

Illustration

Animation

TOOLS

Sketch

Figma

Photoshop

Illustrator

After Effects . . .

Cinema 4D

Axure RP

Keynote

LANGUAGES

Mandarin

English

CAREER OBJECTIVE

A user interface designer with three years of experience in design is seeking an opportunity to make beneficial contribution to a company with enthusiasm and commitment. Knowledgeable in user interface, user experience, user research, prototyping, wireframing and illustrating. Equipped with a diverse and promising skill set. Advanced in an assortment of technologies, including Figma, Sketch, Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects and Azure RP. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

User Interface Designer

Jiezi Technology Co.Ltd | China

June 2018 - Oct 2020

- Took most responsibilities of user-centred design from concept to delivery of most projects, including native mobile APP and responsive websites.
- Created and delivered broader graphic design assets including campaign banners, illustrations, posters etc. to meet the needs of marketing promotions.
- Collaborated with product team on evaluating user requirements and provided wireframes, prototypes and design guidelines to stakeholders.
- Took requirements from stakeholders and delivered designs that solve problems, using feedbacks, data, user research and testing for iterations.
- Collaborated with developers and assisted with quality assurance to make sure the final design has been implemented correctly.

Digital Graphic Designer

PartyBestbuy Pty.Ltd | Sydney

Aug 2016 - Oct 2017

- Took responsibility for product picture library management and refinement.
- Designed templates for product listings and established design specifications.
- Collaborated with product manager and stakeholders and created original designs for branding and related promotional materials.
- Assisted in managing the company's website and acquiring customer feedbacks and ensured consistent iterations that meet the needs of the customer.

EDUCATION

Master of Information Technology

The University of Sydney | Sydney

Jul 2014 - Aug 2015

Achievement: Scored a Distinction in Software Development in Java

Bachelor of Information Technology

Deakin University | Melbourne

Apr 2013 - Jul 2014

 Achievement: Scored High Distinction in Web Programming, Project Management Scored Distinction in Interactive Media Systems, Project